## **TIMOTHY TAIWO ONI**

+2348037740430| timothytaiwooni@gmail.com No. 35, Alhaji Akinremi Adepelu, Okebadan estate, Akobo, Ibadan.

### **CAREER SUMMARY**

Perceptive Individual, pursuing a challenging career in an organization that promotes and encourages the application of my skills, trainings, education and experience in adding value to the attainment of the corporate objectives. Skilled in research and Collaborates with teams to accomplish strategic goals. Unflinching passion for impacting knowledge effectively and with accuracy. Great interpersonal relationship, ability to carry everybody along.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Crest Church Mayfair, Ife, Osun State. Church Administrator

September 2018 till present

- Keep members database for follow up and update
- Handling of finance
- Keeping track of Program and events of the church for the year
- Getting feedback from members.
- Serving as intermediary between members and pastorate.

# ISON BPO Company, Dugbe, Ibadan. Oyo State Customer Care Representative - Airtel Nigeria

May 2015 - January 2017

- Handled inbound calls
- Ensured calls were answered in compliance with predefined parameters.
- Attending to customers complaints and giving due instructions on how to rectify problems

### NYSC Ikwuano L.G.A, Abia State.

# Corps' liaison officer (CLO): Coordination and Administration November 2013 October 2014

- Coordination of corps' members in respect of programs and community development service.
- Dissemination of information and communiqué from state secretariat to corps' members.
- Documentation of corps' members complains and request for prompt action.
- Monthly progress report of events, programs and achievements of the local government and corps members to state secretariat.

- Hosting of visitors and representing the scheme in the host community.
- Orientation of new corps' members.

### OTHER EXPERIENCES:

- Instructor Sure Success Academy, Umuahia, Abia State.
- Intern, Administrative Officer National Orientation Agency, Gombe, Gombe State. 2011

February 2014
March 2011 - April

- Receptionist Okamata Hotels (now Devotion Hotels) Jos, Plateau State.
   2007
- Intern, Clerk Officer Nigeria life pension consultant PLC, Jos, Plateau State.
   2004

February 2007 - December

August 2004 - November

### **VOLUNTARY SERVICES**

# Federation of Colleges Ex-students' Christian Association (FECA NIGERIA) National Outreach Coordinator

**August 2012 - August 2014** 

- Training of leaders, students and youth for self-productivity and national development.
- Training of students for academic excellence.
- Tutoring and organizing of exams for SSCE and JAMB candidate.
- Coordination and supervision of activities, programs and events for secondary students, undergraduate and graduate.
- Supervision of committee that set questions for candidates writing SSCE and JAMB.
- Organizing and coordination of community based program.

### **SKILLS AND EXPERTISE**

- Creative Problem Solving Skills
- Research and Development
- Team Work and Collaboration
- Relational and Communication Skills
- Technical Writing Skills
- Project Management
- Use of Microsoft Office Tools (Ms. Excel, Word, PowerPoint).

### **EDUCATION**

- OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY, ILE IFE, OSUN STATE— Master of Arts in Educational Administration 2018
- UNIVERSITY OF MAIDUGURI, MAIDUGURI, BORNO STATE. B.Ed Adult Education and Business Administration 2013
- PLATEAU STATE POLYTECHNIC, BARKIN LADI.- National Diploma in Business Administration and Management

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS		
• NIGERIA INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT (NIM):	Member	2014
PUBLICATIONS AN	ND THESIS	
THESIS TITLE (An Unpublished M.A. Thesis): Princip	oal's Use of Management Pi	•
Quality Assurance in Osun State Secondary School.		2018
REFERENC	ES	

Available on request.